Guide to Speeches in the Records of the Office of the President (Dr. John Brademas) RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Remarks delivered at the Oregon Council for the Humanities 20th Anniversary Celebration (Portland, OR), 27 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 6)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the Kriser Family Dinner, 30 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 7)
  - Check presentation to the NYU Community Fund, 1 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 8)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 2 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 9)
  - Remarks by L. Jay Oliva on higher education, delivered at a press conference convened by Representative Thomas J. Downey at Dowling College, 3 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 10)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a reception for visiting high school counselors, NYU, 6 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 11)
  - Talking points delivered at the Caring Community Breakfast Meeting, NYU, 8 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 12)
  - Remarks delivered at the Alumni Council Dinner, NYU, 8 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 13)
  - "Higher Education in the Nineties: Prospects & Problems," delivered at the Associates of the Yale Medical Library Annual Meeting, 9 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 14)
  - Remarks delivered at a benefit gala for the America-Italy Society (NYC), 14 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 16)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Institute of Fine Arts Board of Trustess, NYU, 15 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 17)
  - Remarks by Dr. Brademas and Larry Tisch at the Trustees' Pre-Commencement Dinner, NYU, 15 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 18)
  - Remarks delivered at the Alumni Commencement Breakfast, NYU, 16 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 19)
  - Remarks delivered at a ceremony awarding the Albert Gallatin Medal to Thomas S. Murphy, 16 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 20)
  - Remarks delivered upon awarding honorary degrees to Stella Adler, Joan Ganz Cooney, Gianluigi Colalucci, Judith Ann Jamison, Victor Frederick, and others, 16 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 21)
  - Scripts for remarks by Dr. Brademas and Larry Tisch at the 159th Commencement, NYU, 16 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 22)
  - Remraks delivered at the Medical School Last Day Exercises, NYU, 16 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 23)
  - Remarks delivered at a ceremony giving the Pancyprian Association Freedom Award to George Paraskevaides (NYC), 18 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 24)
  - Keynote address delivered at the American Association of Museums 86th Annual Meeting (Denver, CO), 20 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 25)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner celebrating the Department of Dermatology, NYU, 21 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 26)
  - Remarks delivered at the President's Council Reception, NYU, 21 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 27)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting commemorating the 125th anniversary of the College of Dentistry, NYU, 22 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 28)
  - "Key to the 21st Century: Educated Men & Women," delivered as a special lecture at the University of Thessaloniki (Greece), 30 May 1991 (Box 627, Folder 29)
  - "Higher Education: The Global Perspective," delivered at the Wolfson College Symposium on Higher Education (Oxford, England), 7 June 1991 (Box 627, Folder 30)
  - Introduction of Boris Yeltsin, President-Elect of the Russian Federation, NYU, 21 June 1991 (Box 627, Folder 31)
  - Oral testimony delivered before a U.S. House of Representatives Committee on Education & Labor Hearing, NYU, 24 June 1991 (Box 627, Folder 32)
  - Remarks delivered on receiving the NSFRE Award for Achievement in Philanthropy (NYC), 28 June 1991 (Box 627, Folder 33)
  - Message to the School of Law, 1 July 1991 (Box 627, Folder 34)
  - "Education & The Environmental Crisis," delivered at the International Conference on the Environment at the University of Barcelona (Spain), 9 July 1991 (Box 627, Folder 35)